bookeasytrip.com 2016-05-05

# Read Privacy Policy of EaseMyTrip.in

Privacy policy of EaseMyTrip.in practices to handle and secure the Personal Information of its customers. The privacy policy is applicable to persons who purchase any product or services from EaseMyTrip.in through any of its sales channels. This privacy statement doesn’t implement on any website or other third parties that are linked to EaseMyTrip.in Website. We are a trustworthy name in travel industry of India and all the measures to protect your privacy.

To visit the website of EaseMyTrip.in, you don’t need to reveal your personal identification. The user exploring our website can be completely anonymous, if he/she wants to.

**Personal Details We Collect and Their Usage:-**

If you book or purchase any services, sign-up for the newsletters of our website or go for e-commerce transactions, EaseMyTrip.in collects the following personal information from you while transacting: 

* Name
* Contact Number
* Address
* Credit Card details
* Age
* Email I’d 

EaseMyTrip.in does not trade or sell any of the above important & sensitive information without the prior concern of its users or customers. The aforementioned details are collected from the users/customers/travelers for following reasons:

**To Book a Service:-**  
We collect names, addresses, phone numbers, and age details of the users to share with related service providers, including airlines, hotels, or bus services for making their reservations and booking.

**To Send Promotional Offers:-**

Details like mobile numbers and e-mail I’d are used by us for sending information about any ongoing promotional offers. We often conduct lucky draws to give the members a chance to win holiday discounts or travel coupons. If user wants, he can anytime unsubscribe for such emails. In that condition, customers will become oblivious of ongoing promotional discounts. 

**Member Registration:-**

To become a registered member of EaseMyTrip.in, you have to provide details like name, address, phone, e-mail id, a user name and password. This information is taken on the registration form for different reasons like:  
1\. User identification  
2\. To complete the travel bookings  
3\. To get in touch with you to facilitate your specific needs  
4.To improve our products and services  
5.To confirm your each booking you do.  
**Surveys:-** EaseMyTrip.in knows it very well that customers’ opinions matter the most for any business entity. So, it regularly performs surveys using your personal identification information and invites the customers/travelers/users for taking part into the same. Participation in these surveys is not at all essential. These surveys are conducted to know about the users’ experiences with EaseMyTrip.in. Survey participants remain anonymous.

**Safeguard Sensitive Information:-**

Sensitive details like Credit/Debit Card and Net Banking information are primarily collected by the payment gateways and banks and not by EaseMyTrip.in. However, if this information is stored on our site, it remains completely unshared and safe. Sometimes, such information is shared with certain third parties to process the applicable Cashback offers & discounts.

**Automatic Classification of Session Data:-** We trace session data of the users, including IP address, OS, software and user behavior. It helps us in finding out the troubles a user faces with our servers and lets us improve our systems. However, these details do not identify any visitor personally except examining the user’s rough geographic location.

EaseMyTrip.in ensures that the information you share with us is fully protected. Our advance technology, security measures and strict policy guidelines help in securing the privacy of the customers and saving their information from any unwanted access. The privacy policy of EaseMyTrip.in keeps on updating due to various situations and development of technologies. To know about our latest privacy policy, keep checking the website regularly.

Thank you for using EaseMyTrip.in!.
